export const QuestionData = [
    {
        "question": "1. Which of the following is used in React.js to increase performance?",
        "options": ["A) Virtual Dom", "B) Original Dom", "C) Both A and B", "D) None of the Above"],
        "answer": "A) Virtual DOM is used in React.js to increase performance."
    },
    {
        "question": "2. What is ReactJS?",
        "options": ["A) Server-side framework", "B) User interface framework", "C) Both A and B", "D) None of the Above"],
        "answer": "B) ReactJS is a user-interface framework."
    },
    {
        "question": "3. What is ReactJS?",
        "options": ["A) Render with aruguments", "B) setState", "C) PropTypes", "D) Props"],
        "answer": "B) props are used to pass data to components from outside"
    },
    {
        "question": "4. Who created React.js?",
        "options": ["A) Jordan Mike", "B) Jordan Walke", "C) Time Lee", "D) Jordan Lee"],
        "answer": "B) B) Jordan Walke created React.js."
    },
    {
        "question": "5. In which language is React.js written?",
        "options": ["A) Phython", "B) JavaScript", "C) Java", "D)PHP"],
        "answer": "B) React.js is written in Javascript."
    },
    {
        "question": "6. What is Babel?",
        "options": ["A) JavaScript compiler", "B) JavaScript interpreter", "C) JavaScript transpiler", "D)None of the Above"],
        "answer": " A) Devil is a JavaScript compiler"
    },
    {
        "question": "7. Identify the command used to create a react app",
        "options": ["A) npm install create-react-app", "B) npm install -g create-react-app", "C)  install -g create-react-app", "D) None of the Above"],
        "answer": " B) npm install -g create-react-app is used to create a react app"
    },
    {
        "question": "8. Which of the following port is the default where webpack-dev-server runs?",
        "options": ["A) 3000", "B) 3306", "C) 3030", "D) 8080"],
        "answer": "D) 8080 is the default where webpack-dev-server runs."
    },

    {
        "question": "9.How many elements can a valid react component return?",
        "options": ["A) 1", "B) 2", "C) 3", "D) 4"],
        "answer": "A) A valid red component can return only 1 element"
    },
    {
        "question": "10. A state in React.js is also known as?",
        "options": ["A) The internal storage of the component", "B) External storage of the component", "C) Permanat storage", "D) All of the Above"],
        "answer": " A) A state in React.js is also known as the internal storage of the component."
    },
];

